airfasttickets.com 2014-11-21

# AirFastTickets - Privacy Policy

##### AirFastTickets has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the users of our Web Site, www.airfasttickets.com. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from you and all of our visitors and users.

##### PLEASE NOTE THAT BY SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US, AND/OR BY USING OUR WEB SITE, YOU AGREE THAT WE MAY COLLECT, USE AND DISCLOSE SUCH PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND AS PERMITTED OR REQUIRED BY LAW.

##### **INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

##### **Personally Identifiable Information.** We collect personally identifiable information (“Personal Data”) about you that you provide to us while using the Web Site. Personal Data includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name, address, phone number, credit card number, and/or e-mail address. We may also request certain information from you, such as information about your hotel room preferences and frequent flyer programs. You may choose not to provide information to us, but in general some information about you is required in order for you to register with us as member; book travel; complete a traveler profile; participate in a survey, contest, or sweepstakes; ask us a question; or initiate other transactions on our Web Site.

##### **Device and Usage Information.** We automatically collect some information about the devise you are using to visit our Web Site. This information include your computer’s IP address; the web browser used (such as Firefox, Safari, or Internet Explorer); the domain name of the website from which you came; the date, time and duration of your visit to our Web Site; the number of visits to our Web Site; the pages viewed on our Web Site; the cookies accumulated on your browser; the type of mobile device used; and the unique identifier of your mobile device.

##### **Information on Other Travelers.** If you book travel for someone else through Airfasttickets, we will request personal information and travel preferences about that other traveler. You should obtain the consent of other travelers prior to providing us with their personal information and travel preferences, as any access to view or change their information will be available only through your account. By providing any Personal Data of another traveler, you represent that you have all necessary authority and/or have obtained all necessary consents from such person to enable us to collect, use and disclose such Personal Data as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

##### **HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

##### We use Personal Data to provide you with the products and services from our Web Site, including the booking of travel reservations. In addition, we may use your Personal Data to, among other things:   
1\. build features that will make the services available on the Web Site better and more easier to use, including faster purchase requests, better customer support, and timely notice of new services and special offers;   
2\. record your travel preferences so that we can personalize our services to you, tailor your experience on our Web Site to your preferences, and make more appropriate travel recommendations;   
3\. communicate with you about your travel plans;   
4\. issue invoices, administer accounts, collect and process payments;   
5\. notify you if you win when you participate in a contest, promotion, raffle or sweepstakes;   
6\. send you commercial communications (if you have not opted-out of receiving these communications);   
7\. monitor your transactions to send you information about our products and services and other information and materials that may be relevant and of interest to you based on your transactions;   
8\. where necessary, investigate, detect and protect Airfasttickets and Travel Service Providers against error, negligence, breach of contract, fraud, theft and other illegal activities;   
9\. comply with, any legal or regulatory requirements or provisions.

##### **RETAINING AND STORING YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

##### We will retain your Personal Data in our databases in accordance with our records management policy and applicable laws. This period may extend beyond the end of your relationship with us, but it will be only as long as it is necessary for us to have sufficient information to respond to any issues that may arise later. For example, we may need or be required to retain information (i) to allow you to obtain credit for a trip you booked with us, but later had to cancel; (ii) to prevent fraudulent activity; (iii) protect ourselves against liability, permit us to pursue available remedies or limit any damages that we may sustain; or (iv) if we believe in good faith that a law, regulation, rule or guideline requires it. Your Personal Data will be stored in secured locations and on servers controlled by Airfasttickets, located either at our offices or at the offices of our service providers.

##### **PROTECTING YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

##### To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of Personal Data, we will employ reasonable and current internet security methods and technologies. To protect credit and card transactions while in transit, we currently use Secure Socket Layer technology to encrypt Personal Data.

##### **SHARING YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

##### We do not share your Personal Data, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy or unless we receive your prior consent. Where necessary, Airfasttickets may, however, share your Personal Data as follows:   
• With Travel Service Providers, such as hotels, airlines, car rental companies, and cruise lines, that fulfill your travel reservations. We do not share your email address with Travel Service Providers unless it is needed to fulfill your reservation, and we restrict the use of this information to that purpose. Travel Service Providers have their own privacy policies, and you are encouraged to review the relevant privacy policies of any Travel Service Provider whose products you purchase through this Web Site.   
• To third parties providing services or functions on our behalf, including credit card processing, marketing, advertising, distribution of surveys or sweepstakes programs, and fraud prevention. These third parties have access to and may collect Personal Data only as needed to perform their functions and are not permitted to share or use the Personal Data for any other purpose. They are also required to follow the same data security practices that we ourselves adhere to.   
• Business partners with whom we may jointly offer products or services, or whose products or services may be offered on our website, may receive your Personal Data in connection with offering those products or services.   
• If you are referred to our Web Site by another websites by, for example, clicking a link on that other website, we may share some of your Personal Data with that other website. You are encouraged to review the privacy policies of any website that referred you here.   
• Your Personal Data may be shared with companies within our corporate family, which enables us to provide you with information about products and services, both travel-related and other, which might interest you.   
• Our business is constantly changing, and as part of that process, we may sell or buy other companies. Personal Data may be transferred as part of these transactions. It is also possible that all or some of our assets may be acquired by another company, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, and Personal Data may be transferred as part of such a transaction. • In order to comply with applicable laws and other requirements, we reserve the right to release Personal Data, including whenever we believe that disclosure is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on Airfasttickets.   
• We may also release Personal Data to enforce or apply the terms and conditions applicable to our products and services, protect us or others against fraudulent or inappropriate activities, or otherwise protect the rights, property or safety of Airfasttickets, our affiliated companies, our customers, or others.   
Please be aware that, if your Personal Data is shared with third parties pursuant to this Privacy Policy, such third parties may be located outside of the United States in countries which may not provide for the same level of protection as the laws in your home jurisdiction.

##### **COOKIES POLICY**

##### **What Are Cookies?**

##### We use cookies on our Web Site to create the most secure and effective website possible for our customers. Among other things, cookies allow you to log on to our booking platform, choose log-in preferences, apply for products and services online and use online tools. Cookies are small bits of code, usually stored on a user’s computer hard drive or device, which enable a web site to “personalize” itself for each user by remembering information about the user’s visit to the web site. Cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience on our Web Site.

##### **How Are Cookies Used?**

##### Cookies are used for a variety of reasons, such as to safeguard your privacy when browsing the Web Site. They allow you to use functions such as secure online applications. If you leave a secure session window open, cookies will enhance your security by prompting you to end, and/or automatically ending, your secure session. Cookies can also allow us to tailor the content of our Web Site to suit your interests. For example, instead of displaying promotional messages about products you already have, they let us show you other services in which you may be interested. Finally, we use “analytics” cookies to help us make our Web Site better for those who visit it regularly. Cookies help us work out what users like and don't like, and how we can improve things for you.

##### **Working With Third Parties.**

##### No third party has access to the information we collect through the cookies, and we only use cookies from third parties in order to provide our customers with our products and services. The only time cookies would enable us to share your information is when you have given us express consent to pass it on to a trusted third party.   
We may, however, share Web Site usage information about visitors to our Web Sites with these third parties for the purpose of managing and targeting advertisements and for market research analysis on our Web Site and other web sites. For these purposes, we and our third-party advertising companies may place pixel tags (also called clear gifs) on some of the pages you visit on our Web Site. We will then use the non-personally identifiable information that is collected using these pixel tags to serve you relevant advertisements when you are visiting other web sites on the Internet. These advertisements may be targeted to specific searches you conducted on the Web Site during earlier browsing sessions. If you do not want to receive these advertisements, marketing material or other offers, please send us an email at info@airfasttickets.com.

##### **Managing Your Cookies.**

##### The browsers of most computers, smartphones and other web-enabled devices are typically set up to accept cookies. If you wish to amend your cookie preferences for this Web Site or any other web sites, you can do this through your browser settings. Your browser’s “help” function will tell you how to do this. However, please remember that cookies are often used to enable and improve certain functions on our Web Site. If you choose to switch certain cookies off, it is likely to affect how our Web Site works.   
If you have any questions about the use of cookies, please contact us at info@airfasttickets.com.

##### **MARKETING MATERIAL AND ADVERTISEMENTS**

##### Unless you tell us that you do not want to receive these offers, Airfasttickets or those companies with which we have a commercial relationship, may occasionally send advertisements, marketing material or other offers that we think might be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive these advertisements, marketing material or other offers, please send us an email at info@airfasttickets.com.

##### **NOTICES AND FEEDBACK AND OPTING-OUT**

##### From time to time, we may contact you to request feedback on your experience using the Web Site, to assist us in improving the Web Site, or to offer special savings or promotions to you, as a Web Site user. If you would prefer not to receive notices of special savings or promotions, you may simply opt-out from receiving them by sending us an email at info@airfasttickets.com.

##### **EXTERNAL LINKS**

##### When we include links to other websites, please bear in mind they will have their own privacy and cookie policies that will govern the use of any information you submit. We recommend you read their policies as we are not responsible or liable for their privacy practices.

##### **SOCIAL MEDIA**

##### Our Web Site includes plug-ins to social media sites such as Facebook or Twitter, and gives you the option to post information about your products and services you purchase from our Web Site to your social media accounts. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Web Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. In addition, by linking your social media account to our Web Site, we may collect information such as your name, email address, profile picture, gender, list of friends, and other information that you authorize us to receive. Social plug-ins are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Web Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.

##### **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

##### We may update this Privacy Policy in the future. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the email address you provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

##### **CONTACT US**

##### If you have questions about either this Privacy Policy (or your travel planning or purchases), please contact us at info@airfasttickets.com.
